# Helping great companies to build epic apps & websites



Hi, I'm Fernando Guevara. A UX/UI designer currently bringing to life simple and elegant experiences at Acklen Avenue.

For the last 6 years i have been building awesome software products and services hand-to-hand with developers and multi-functional teams across different industries.

My approach is based on User-Centered design and Lean / Agile methodologies. Learning from users first, identify and validate hypotheses that work and test ideas as soon as possible.

The goal is to create things people want to use and they will actually buy.

# **Experience**

### **UX/UI Designer**

Acklen Avenue

Aug 2015 - Present

• Conducting user research and testing • Gathering and evaluating user needs, in collaboration with product managers and clients. • Understanding business requirements and any technical limitations. • Developing wireframes and task flows, UI mockups and prototypes based on user needs. • Collaborating with other designers and Developers to create intuitive, user-friendly software.

### **Quality Assurance Engineer**

Acklen Avenue

Jun 2015 - Aug 2015

 Reviewing quality specifications and technical design documents to provide timely and meaningful feedback.
Creating detailed, comprehensive and well-structured test plans and test cases.
Estimating, prioritizing, planning and coordinating quality testing activities.

### **HTML & CSS Administrator**

Laureate Int. Universities

Apr 2014 - Jun 2015

- Translate and maintain company's visual style guidelines.
- Executing all visual design stages from concept to final hand-off to engineering. Conceptualizing original website design ideas that bring simplicity and user friendliness to complex roadblocks.

# Web & Mobile designer

Freelance

Apr 2013 - Feb 2014

• Design conversion-oriented websites for different companies. • Create digital marketing materials. • Design user-friendly interfaces for mobile applications • Enhance client's brand through digital solutions understanding market needs

# Skills & knowledge

## Research & strategy

Agile	Usability test	Information Architecture		
Google Analytics Content Strategy				
SEO	A/B testing	A/B testing		

### Design

Sketch App	Adobe CC	Prototyping
Wireframing	Branding	Principle
IOS interface design	Materia	al design

# Code

HTML	CSS	Javascript	SASS
Git/terminal	JQuery	Resposive I	Design

### Other skills i've develop

Learner	Passion for the web		User is always right
Humilty	Team work	Make p	people smile :)

# **Education**

# UNITEC

2008 - 2012

Graphic Design, Bachelor's degree.

# Languages

English

Spanish